# **Your next employee**: thorough and experienced problem solver to the position as <u>Product Manager</u>

Hi, my name is Joel Gjerde, I am a person who really is passionate about my work, and I take it very seriously.

I am an active person who plays hockey and floorball in my spare time. In addition to sports, I have 2 children and a wife who I live with in Norrahammar for 1.5 years.

Im currently working as Supervisor for TIP Nordic in the Roadside Nordic department.

I would describe myself as thorough, structured, independent and love to solve problems, both short and long term. Based on what you wrote in the job description, I therefore believe that I am the right person for you!

In addition to my current job, I have previously been involved in starting JG Software AB which is a software company that specializes in solutions for the transport industry. The company also worked with IT consultation for our customers, with everything from network installations to troubleshooting, system integrations, and building completely new ERP systems with customer specifications.

I am used to working under deadlines and hard pressure and am flexible with working hours so that it benefits my colleagues.



#### **Details**

21 November 1991

Parkvillan 7 56230 Norrahammar Sweden

+46 (0) 73 088 21 34 joel@gjerdeinvest.se

#### Language

Norwegian writing & speaking - ground level

<u>Danish</u> writing & speaking - ground level

Swedish writing & speaking - fluent

English writing & speaking - fluent

### **Educations**

Medborgarskolan i Helsingborg (course) 2015 Accountancy

John Bauer (high school) 2007 - 2010 IT- Network & Programing

## Work experience

TIP Trailer Services Sweden AB (Jönköping)

Feb 2020 - current

Supervisor, Road assistance, Process manager

TIP Trailer Services Denmark ApS (Köpenhamn)

Jul 2018 - Feb 2020

Team leader, Road assistance

JG Software AB (Helsingborg)

Aug 2015 - Jul 2018

Co-founder and CEO

PNO Sverige AB (Helsingborg)

Feb 2015 - Aug 2015

**Equipment Controller** 

PNO Sverige AB (Helsingborg)

Jul 2013 - Feb 2015

**Equipment Coordinator** 

PNO Sverige AB (Göteborg)

Feb 2013 - Jul 2013

Acting workshop manager

PNO Sverige AB (Jönköping)

Aug 2012 - Feb 2013

Customer recipient, Supervisor evening shift

Voss Vandrarheim (Voss, Norge)

Jan 2011 - Jun 2012

Night porter

Voss Resort AS (Voss, Norge)

Nov 2010 - May 2012

Lift guard

Voss Kommune (Voss, Norge)

Nov 2010 - Mar 2012

Personal assistant

PNO Sverige AB (Jönköping)

Dec 2009 - Sep 2010

**Trailer mechanic**